You sightings is an essential part of System UI.
It's mainly responsible for opening and closing of the functional modules of each system, such as Wi-Fi,
Bluetooth, flashlight, etc...
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
Before we start looking at the court, let me quickly show you Duke sitting silent.
So in the phone, when we drag from top to bottom, you can see these tiny windows, right?
And each of these styles are actually responsible for some of the system settings.
For example, if I need to switch on the flashlight, I click on this right.
Similarly, being the do not disturb the system will going to be being demoed.
And similarly, airplane mode and many other features sort of like the Bluetooth to the next tab, where
you have other options like location, battery saver.
So this new setting style window has basically two functionalities.
One is to display all these styles, and the second option is to customize this time.
When you click on that button, it goes through an 80 page and you can actually customize, exemplify,
need to bring internet.
The little window, I could bring it here like this.
And if I need to put internet at all, I can rearrange it like this here if I come back and open the
settings again.
I have the internet I'll window available for waking up.
So in summary, the UK's settings has a features.
The first feature is the load or these system settings and display to the user like this, and it also
provides an option to customize that by clicking on this edit.
Now, let's dig deeper into the code and see which modules are actually responsible to initialize each
of these settings.
All the Quick Settings related modules can be found under System UI.
US Package Secure stands for Quick Settings.
Yes is the short phone for Settings, so I only introduce some of the most important classes that you
should know when working with Click Settings, but the first one is US Panel.
UAC Panel is the view that represents the quick setting tile panel, so this view is actually responsible
for showing I'll do the them.
So to make it more clear, this view is entire view is actually implemented with this guest panel glass.
As we can see here, the US panel extends a linear layout.
Another important classes US style host, the Q Style host is actually responsible for creating pilots.
So here we can see the create tile function, which actually is responsible for creating the guys in
the US panel.
We look at this class a little bit closer when we look at the loading process of ice.
Another important classes style AM bill, so this is an abstract class.
Again, find it under this tile and be a package for gear style ambient.
So this is basically an abstract class which is implemented or extended by all the tiles.
So if we come to these tiles each year, we can see all the tiles.
So in this nice package, there will be a class for each of these tile like sample internet.
So for internet, there will be a tile here.
Internet tile.
This one and for another one airplane mode and see the airplane mode tile here.
Alarm tile is here.
Is this one?
So for each of these tile, there will be a corresponding glass here, which contains the implementation
logic of this time and each of these glass.
They open this airplane mode, tile or tower.
Then we can see that it extends Swiss style ambient to the Cuban and bill.
He's basically an abstract glass, which has all the required abstract methods to implement a particular
time.
We can see all the tile classes extend skewer style and build glass, but there are many other packages
as well within the US module to a package like guide your customized diagram.
So the Customize package contains two classes for the masterminds view, as we have seen earlier.
There is an option to customize the tiles so those implementation can be found here and then the dagger.
Dagger contains the dagger dependency implementation, dependency injection implementation for this
particular module, and then there are something related to external.
So these contain some tiles service manager, bi lifecycle manager, etc. and the Logging Gears logo
and the dialer and bill.
As we have seen, it's the abstract class which is actually extended by all the times, and the tiles
contains a nice package, contains all the tiles.
So for each of the tile, there will be a corresponding class which extends the CPU asylum.
Then finally, there is some package for that.
So this is something to handle the gesture detection like.
So that was a quick overview of the modules which are found in the Settings package.
Wow.
Wow, wow.